Register of the Milton Friedman papers 77011.4088897
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1940-1991 (Boxes 6-35)
  - Bowen, Howard R., 1951-1953. (Box-folder 21: 15)
    Includes correspondence with John H. Williams.
  - Bowen, William G., 1958-1961 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Bowman, Ward S., 1958-1972 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Brady, Dorothy S., 1948-1957 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - Brady, William H., Jr., 1960-1967 (Box-folder 21: 19)
  - Brand, Lawrence H., 1970-1977 (Box-folder 21: 20)
  - Brand, Stewart, 1977 (Box-folder 21: 21)
  - Brandenburg, R. O., 1973-1979 (Box-folder 21: 22)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1949-1960 (Box-folder 21: 23)
  - Braun, Julius, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 21: 24)
  - Breen, Nancy, 1951-1973 (Box-folder 21: 25)
  - Breit, William, 1964-1979 (Box-folder 21: 26)
  - Brennan, Michael J., 1959-1963 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    Includes correspondence with George L. Mehren.
  - Brill, Daniel H., 1965-1969 (Box-folder 21: 28)
  - Brimmer, Andrew F., 1973 (Box-folder 21: 29)
  - Brinegar, George K., 1951-1952 (Box-folder 21: 30)
  - Brinkley, David, 1974 (Box-folder 21: 31)
  - Brittain, John A., 1959-1970 (Box-folder 21: 32)
  - Brittan, Samuel (Financial Times, London), 1958-1978 (Box-folder 21: 33)
  - Broida, Arthur L., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 21: 34)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, 1947-1977 (Box-folder 21: 35)
  - Brookes, Warren T., 1976 (Box-folder 21: 36)
  - Brookings Institution (Robert D. Calkins), 1956-1965 (Box-folder 21: 37)
  - Brown, Elizabeth R., 1978 (Box-folder 21: 38)
  - Brown, Francis J., 1964 (Box-folder 21: 39)
  - Brown, George H., 1964 (Box-folder 21: 40)
  - Brown, Leon B., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 21: 41)
  - Brown, Sidney, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 21: 42)
  - Brown, Winton, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 21: 43)
  - Brownlee, Oswald H., 1951-1962 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Broyde, Samuel, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Brozen, Yale, 1950-1968 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Brunie, Charles H., 1968-1977 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Brunner, Karl, 1956-1978 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Bryan, Malcolm, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Bryant, Ralph C., 1976 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Bubeck, C. H., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    Includes correspondence with Harry C. Eastman.
  - Buchanan, James M., 1951-1977 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Buchanan, Norman S., 1958 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Buchanan, Patrick J., 1973 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Buckley, James L., 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1961-1979 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Budzyner, Simon, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Bunting, Robert L., 1955-1974 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Burns, Arthur F., 1947-1972 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - Burns, Joseph M., 1960-1979 (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Burstein, Meyer L., 1960-1978 (Box-folder 22: 18)
  - Burtle, James, 1958 (Box-folder 22: 19)
  - Business Week, 1956-1966 (Box-folder 22: 20)
  - Busler, Michael R., 1976-1979 (Box-folder 22: 21)
  - Butler, Arthur, 1959 (Box-folder 22: 22)
  - Butz, Earl L., 1975 (Box-folder 22: 23)
  - Caffè, Federico, 1965 (Box-folder 22: 24)
  - Cagan, Phillip D., 1952-1978 (Box-folder 22: 25)
  - Cameron, Rondo E., 1951-1964 (Box-folder 22: 26)
    Includes correspondence with John Perry Miller.
  - Campaigne, Jameson G., Jr., 1977 (Box-folder 22: 27)
  - Campbell, Albert M., 1978 (Box-folder 22: 28)
  - Campbell, Burnham O., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 22: 29)
  - Campbell, Colin D., 1949-1973 (Box-folder 22: 30)
    Includes correspondence with Ralph E. Conwell.
  - Campbell, W. Glenn, 1955-1972 (Box-folder 22: 31)
  - Cargill, Thomas F., 1977 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Carlson, Sune, 1947-1955 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Carr, Jack, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Carson, Deane, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Cate, James L., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Chamberlin, Edward H., 1948-1960 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Chapin, Ned, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Chase, Samuel (and Lyle Gramley), 1965 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Cheadle, Harold L., 1958-1961 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Chipman, John S., 1957-1964 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Chiswick, Barry R., 1975 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Chow, Gregory C., 1957-1973 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Christ, Carl F., 1949-1979 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Christenson, Charles, 1973 (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - Circ, Ljubo, 1973 (Box-folder 23: 17)
  - Claassen, Emil Maria, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - Clark, Clifford D., 1952-1975 (Box-folder 23: 19)
  - Clark, Colin, 1948-1978 (Box-folder 23: 20)
  - Clark, John M., 1952-1961 (Box-folder 23: 21)
  - Clark, Lincoln, 1949-1956 (Box-folder 23: 22)
  - Clark, Lindley H., Jr. (Wall Street Journal), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 23: 23)
  - Clawson, Del, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 24)
  - Clise, J. Ward, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 23: 25)
  - Cloos, George W., 1959 (Box-folder 23: 26)
  - Clower, Robert W., 1959-1976 (Box-folder 23: 27)
  - Coase, Ronald H., 1948-1976 (Box-folder 23: 28)
  - Cochran, William G., 1937-1950 (Box-folder 23: 29)
  - Cohan, Avery B., 1958-1977 (Box-folder 23: 30)
  - Cohen, Wilbur J., 1971 (Box-folder 23: 31)
  - Colberg, Marshall R., 1959-1961 (Box-folder 23: 32)
  - Colean, Miles L., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23: 33)
  - Colgate Conservative Club, 1966 (Box-folder 23: 34)
  - Collier, Robert P., 1971-1974 (Box-folder 23: 35)
  - Collier's Yearbook (William T. Couch), 1954-1955 (Box-folder 23: 36)
  - Columbia Owl, 1964 (Box-folder 23: 37)
  - Columbia University (Horace Taylor), 1946-1951 (Box-folder 23: 38)
  - Conard, Joseph W., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Congdon, Tim, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Connally, John, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Constantacatos, M. E., 1955-1963 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Cook, Paul W., Jr., 1966 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Cooper, Randall H., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Copeland, Morris A. (Cornell University), 1949-1961 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Corn, Ira G., Jr., 1975-1982 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Cornuelle, Richard C., 1956-1963 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Cortney, Philip, 1950-1964 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Court, Andrew T., 1956-1979 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Coutsoumaris, George, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Cox, Albert H., Jr., 1965-1971 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Cox, Garfield V., 1951-1969 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Cramer, Ronald E., 1971-1977 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Cramton, Roger C., 1962 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Crane, Edward H., 1977 (Box-folder 24: 17)
  - Crane, Philip M., 1965-1978 (Box-folder 24: 18)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1978 (Box-folder 24: 19)
  - Creamer, Daniel, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 24: 20)
  - Crouch, Robert L., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24: 21)
  - Crum, W. L., 1949 (Box-folder 24: 22)
  - Culbertson, John M., 1959-1966 (Box-folder 24: 23)
  - Cunnyngham, Jon, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 24: 24)
  - Currie, Lauchlin, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 25)
  - Currier, Frederick P., 1966-1978 (Box-folder 24: 26)
  - Curtis, Carl T., 1974-1978 (Box-folder 24: 27)
  - Curtis, Thomas B., 1960-1967 (Box-folder 24: 28)
  - Curtis, Thomas E., Jr., 1976-1979 (Box-folder 24: 29)
  - Cutler, Preston S., 1960 (Box-folder 24: 30)
  - Cyert, Richard M., 1974 (Box-folder 24: 31)
  - Daane, J. Dewey, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralph, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Dale, Edwin L., Jr., 1969-1974 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Daly, Donald J., 1951-1975 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Dannenmeyer, William E., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Darby, Michael R., 1972-1978 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Davenport, John, 1959-1979 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Davidson, Ralph K., 1952 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Davies, Gethyn, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Davis, Joseph S., 1956-1968 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Dean, Charles R., 1958-1962 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Dean, Joel, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Deaver, John V., 1957-1961 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 1976 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - De Fremery, Robert, 1947-1975 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Dehmlow, Louis H. T., 1960-1972 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Delcour, David W., 1963-1966 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Deming, W. Edwards, 1949-1969 (Box-folder 25: 18)
  - Dennison, Stanley, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 25: 19)
  - Dewald, William G., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 25: 20)
  - Director, Aaron, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 25: 21)
  - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1965 (Box-folder 25: 22)
  - Doblin, Ernest M., 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25: 23)
  - Donald, Gordon, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 25: 24)
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1951-1963 (Box-folder 25: 25)
  - Douglass, Paul F. (American University), 1950 (Box-folder 25: 26)
  - Drèze, Jacques H., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 25: 27)
  - Dure, Leon, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 25: 28)
  - Duesenberry, James S., 1952-1960 (Box-folder 25: 29)
  - Earhart Foundation (Richard A. Ware), 1953-1966 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Earley, James S., 1951 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Ecker-Racz, Laszlo L., 1951 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Economic Club of Chicago, 1964 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Egle, Walter, 1949-1966 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Eicher, Jean-Claude, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Eisner, Robert, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Ellender, Allen J., 1963 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Elliott, G. Alex, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Elliott, Roy, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Ellis, Howard, 1947-1957 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Ellsworth, Robert F., 1965 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Emmer, Robert E., 1964 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Enke, Stephen, 1955-1963 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Ensley, Grover W., 1948-1960 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Enthoven, Alain, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 16)
  - Epstein, Ralph C., 1949-1958 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Erlenborn, John N., 1966 (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Ethics (Charles Perry), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 26: 19)
  - Evans, G. Heberton, Jr., 1947-1960 (Box-folder 26: 20)
  - Fand, David I. and Sally, 1948-1972 (Box-folder 26: 21)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (Edison H. Cramer), 1959 (Box-folder 26: 22)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 26: 23)
  - Feige, Edgar, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 26: 24)
  - Fellner, William, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 26: 25)
  - Ferber, Robert, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 26: 26)
  - Fertig, Lawrence, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 26: 27)
  - Fishburn, Peter C., 1991 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Fisher, Malcolm R., 1955-1976 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1976 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Fortune (John McDonald), 1952-1961 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Foster, Philip, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Frankel, S. Herbert, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Frechtling, John A., 1955 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Free Society Association, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Freeman, Gaylord A., Jr., 1961-1976 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Freeman, Harold A., 1949 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Friend, Irwin, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Fulbright, J. W., 1955 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1951-1972 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Garvy, George, 1949-1972 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Gaylord, Clayton R., 1959 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Ghez, Gilbert, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Gideonse, Max, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 27: 17)
  - Gifford, John K., 1966 (Box-folder 27: 18)
  - Ginzberg, Eli, 1947-1955 (Box-folder 27: 19)
  - Glassburner, Bruce, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 27: 20)
  - Goldenthal, Adolph J. (Economic Cooperation Administration), 1951-1961 (Box-folder 27: 21)
  - Goldsmith, Raymond W. and Selma F., 1949-1962 (Box-folder 27: 22)
  - Goldstein, Henry N., 1961 (Box-folder 27: 23)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 27: 24)
  - Gomberg, William, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 27: 25)
  - Gordon, H. Scott, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 27: 26)
  - Gordon, R. Aaron, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 27: 27)
  - Gorman, W. M., 1960 (Box-folder 27: 28)
  - Gorter, Wytze, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 27: 29)
  - Guillebaud, C. W., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 27: 30)
  - Haberler, Gottfried, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 27: 31)
  - Hagen, Everett E., 1949-1956 (Box-folder 27: 32)
  - Haley, Bernard F., 1950-1961 (Box-folder 27: 33)
  - Hamburger, William, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 27: 34)
  - Hamilton, Earl J., 1950-1965 (Box-folder 27: 35)
  - Hammond, Bray, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 27: 36)
  - Harberger, Arnold, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 27: 37)
  - Harbison, Frederick (Princeton University), 1956-1960 (Box-folder 27: 38)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1951-1979 (Box-folder 27: 39)
  - Harper, F. A., 1959-1961 (Box-folder 27: 40)
  - Harper's Magazine (John Fischer), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 27: 41)
  - Harris, Seymour E., 1948-1961 (Box-folder 27: 42)
  - Harriss, C. Lowell, 1946-1962 (Box-folder 27: 43)
  - Hart, Albert G., 1949-1961 (Box-folder 27: 44)
  - Hasson, Joseph A., 1962-1969 (Box-folder 27: 45)
  - Hatanaka, Michio, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Hazlitt, Henry, 1953 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Heflebower, Richard B., 1949-1958 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Heller, Walter W., 1949-1976 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Henig, Harry, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Hester, Donald D., 1963 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Hildreth, Clifford, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 28: 8)
  - Hill, W. W., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  - Hilton, George W., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Hindley, Brian V., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Hirshleifer, Jack, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Hodgman, Donald R., 1960-1963 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Hoff, Trygve J. B. (Farmand), 1950-1964 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Holben, Ralph E., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Holmes, Rolland W., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Homan, Paul T., 1958-1962 (Box-folder 28: 17)
  - Hoselitz, Bert F., 1963-1972 (Box-folder 28: 18)
  - Hotelling, Harold, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 28: 19)
  - Hough, Louis, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 28: 20)
  - Houthakker, Hendrik S., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 28: 21)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1958 (Box-folder 28: 22)
  - Institut de Science Economique Appliquée (Pierre Pujade), 1947 (Box-folder 28: 23)
  - Institut de Statistique de l'Université de Paris, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 28: 24)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 28: 25)
  - Ivarsson, Sven-Ivar, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 28: 26)
  - Jacoby, Neil H., 1955-1976 (Box-folder 28: 27)
  - Jahn, William A., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 28: 28)
  - Japan Economic Research Center (Jiro Enjoji), 1964 (Box-folder 28: 29)
  - Jaszi, George, 1950-1972 (Box-folder 28: 30)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1966 (Box-folder 28: 31)
  - Johnson, Dudley W., 1954-1964 (Box-folder 28: 32)
  - Johnson, Harry G., 1956-1976 (Box-folder 28: 33)
  - Johnson, Thomas F. (American Enterprise Association), 1961-1972 (Box-folder 28: 34)
  - Jones, Alice (Mrs. Homer), 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28: 35)
  - Jones, Homer, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 28: 36)
  - Journal of Economic History, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 28: 37)
  - Journal of Political Economy (Robert A. Mundell, Albert Rees), 1957-1966 (Box-folder 28: 38)
  - Journal of the American Statistical Association (Dale W. Jorgenson, William G. Madow), 1949-1966 (Box-folder 28: 39)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 28: 40)
  - Kafka, Alexandre, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Kane, Edward J., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 29: 2)
  - Kaplan, Marshall, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - Kareken, John H., 1958-1965 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Kauder, Emil, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Kefauver, Estes, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Kelley, Augustus M., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Kemp, Arthur, 1954-1964 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Kenen, Peter B., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - Keran, Michael, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Kershaw, Joseph A., 1952-1955 (Box-folder 29: 11)
  - Kessel, Reuben A., 1953-1962 (Box-folder 29: 12)
  - Ketchem, Marshall D., 1949-1962 (Box-folder 29: 13)
  - Keyfitz, Nathan, 1940 (Box-folder 29: 14)
  - Kilberg, Edward J., 1951-1958 (Box-folder 29: 15)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A., 1951-1964 (Box-folder 29: 16)
  - Kindahl, James K., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 29: 17)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1958 (Box-folder 29: 18)
  - Kitamura, Hiroshi, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 29: 19)
  - Klarman, Herbert E., 1948-1965 (Box-folder 29: 20)
  - Klein, John J., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 29: 21)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., 1953 (Box-folder 29: 22)
  - Knowles, Ruth Sheldon, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 29: 23)
  - Koopmans, Tjalling C., 1955-1957 (Box-folder 29: 24)
  - Kozelka, Richard L., 1948-1954 (Box-folder 29: 25)
  - Kreml, Franklin M., 1956-1970 (Box-folder 29: 26)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1972 (Box-folder 29: 27)
  - Kuh, Edwin, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 29: 28)
  - Kuznets, Simon S., 1946-1961 (Box-folder 29: 29)
  - Laidler, David, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 29: 30)
  - Laird, Melvin R., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 29: 31)
  - Lakatos, Imre, 1973 (Box-folder 29: 32)
  - Landau, Peter, 1964 (Box-folder 29: 33)
  - Lary, Hal B., 1963 (Box-folder 29: 34)
  - Latané, Henry Allan, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 29: 35)
  - Latsis, Spiro J., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 29: 36)
  - Law, William L., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 29: 37)
  - Lees, Dennis K., 1964-1966 (Box-folder 29: 38)
  - Leftwich, Richard H., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 29: 39)
  - Lerner, Abba P., 1959-1963 (Box-folder 29: 40)
  - Lerner, Eugene, 1952-1964 (Box-folder 29: 41)
  - Lester, Richard A., 1950-1962 (Box-folder 29: 42)
  - Letwin, William, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 29: 43)
  - Levy, David, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 29: 44)
  - Levy, Jerome, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 29: 45)
  - Lewis, H. Gregg, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 29: 46)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1966 (Box-folder 29: 47)
  - Lin, An-loh, 1968 (Box-folder 29: 48)
  - Lipsett, Don, 1972 (Box-folder 29: 49)
  - Liviatan, Nissan, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 29: 50)
  - London School of Economics (Alexander M. Carr-Saunders, Lionel C. Robbins), 1951 (Box-folder 29: 51)
  - Lutz, Friedrich A., 1950-1957 (Box-folder 29: 52)
  - Macesich, George, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - Machlup, Fritz, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - Macmillan Company, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - Macy, C. Ward, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - Madden, Carl E., 1966 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Madow, William G., 1950-1961 (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Markowitz, Harry, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - Martin, William McC., 1955-1962 (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - Marty, Alvin L., Jr., 1960-1966 (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - Mason, Edward S., 1954-1961 (Box-folder 30: 10)
  - Mayer, Thomas, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 30: 11)
  - McGraw Hill Book Company, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 30: 12)
  - McKean, Roland N., 1949-1960 (Box-folder 30: 13)
  - McNamara, Pat, 1959 (Box-folder 30: 14)
  - Meade, James, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 30: 15)
  - Meerman, Jacob, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 30: 16)
  - Meigs, A. James, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 30: 17)
  - Meiklejohn, Donald, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 30: 18)
  - Meiselman, David, 1955-1972 (Box-folder 30: 19)
  - Meltzer, Allan H., 1959-1972 (Box-folder 30: 20)
  - Mendershausen, Horst, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 30: 21)
  - Merriam, John F., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 30: 22)
  - Metzler, Lloyd A., 1950 (Box-folder 30: 23)
  - Meyer, John R. (and Edwin Kuh), 1956-1962 (Box-folder 30: 24)
  - Mikesell, Raymond F., 1957-1964 (Box-folder 30: 25)
  - Millikan, Max F., 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30: 26)
  - Milliman, J. W., 1961 (Box-folder 30: 27)
  - Mills, Frederick C., 1947-1952 (Box-folder 30: 28)
  - Mills, Wilbur D., 1955 (Box-folder 30: 29)
  - Mishan, Edward, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 30: 30)
  - Mitchell, George W., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 30: 31)
  - Modern Age (Eugene Davidson), 1960-1964 (Box-folder 30: 32)
  - Mohrman, P. C., 1952-1961 (Box-folder 30: 33)
  - Moore, William H., 1951 (Box-folder 30: 34)
  - Morrison, George R., 1959-1966 (Box-folder 30: 35)
  - Morrison, Jay, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 30: 36)
  - Mosteller, Frederick, 1948-1960 (Box-folder 30: 37)
  - Multer, Abraham J., 1962 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Murphey, Dwight D., 1964 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Murphy, Henry C., 1958 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Murphy, J. Carter, 1949-1963 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Naddeo, Alighiero, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - National Planning Association, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - Neisser, Hans, 1947-1965 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Nerlove, Marc, 1950-1976 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - New York University (Howard L. Adelson), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Newman, Frank C., 1958-1976 (Box-folder 31: 10)
  - Nicholls, William H., 1958 (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Nichols, Russell T., 1946-1964 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - North, Douglass C., 1958-1962 (Box-folder 31: 13)
  - Northwestern Young Conservative Club, 1964 (Box-folder 31: 14)
  - Noyes, Guy E., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - Nutter, G. Warren, 1950-1972 (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - Obst, Maxwell, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 31: 17)
  - Oi, Walter Y., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 31: 18)
  - Okun, Arthur M., 1956-1960 (Box-folder 31: 19)
  - Pai, M. R., 1964 (Box-folder 31: 20)
  - Papandreou, Andreas G., 1958-1962 (Box-folder 31: 21)
  - Pardridge, William D., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 31: 22)
  - Patin, Edgard, 1966 (Box-folder 31: 23)
  - Patinkin, Don, 1948-1974 (Box-folder 31: 24)
  - Patman, Wright, 1964 (Box-folder 31: 25)
  - Pechman, Joseph A., 1953 (Box-folder 31: 26)
  - Percy, Charles H., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 31: 27)
  - Perlman, Mark, 1955 (Box-folder 31: 28)
  - Perlman, Morris, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 31: 29)
  - Perroux, Frangois, 1947-1957 (Box-folder 31: 30)
  - Pesek, Boris, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 31: 31)
  - Peterson, William H., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 31: 32)
  - Pfouts, R. W., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 31: 33)
  - Philbrook, Clarence E., 1948-1964 (Box-folder 31: 34)
  - Phillips, A. William, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 31: 35)
  - Poole, William, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 31: 36)
  - Porter, Charles O., 1959 (Box-folder 31: 37)
  - Predetti, Adalberto, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 31: 38)
  - Prest, Alan R., 1948-1958 (Box-folder 31: 39)
  - Princeton University Press (Herbert S. Bailey, Jr.), 1956-1963 (Box-folder 31: 40)
  - Pritchard, Leland J., 1947-1963 (Box-folder 31: 41)
  - Proxmire, William, 1960 (Box-folder 31: 42)
  - Ramana, Duvvuri V., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Read, Leonard E., 1957-1966 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Relm Foundation [See: Earhart Foundation]
  - Revista de occidente, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Riefler, Winfield W., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - Risch, Walter F., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Robbins, Lionel C., 1951-1977 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Robinson, Clark, 1957 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Rockford College, 1959 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Rolfe, Sidney E., 1949-1956 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Rolph, Earl R., 1952-1956 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Rosenblatt, David, 1946-1951 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Rosten, Leo C., 1947-1959 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Rottenberg, Simon, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Royal Economic Society, 1959 (Box-folder 32: 14)
  - Royster, Vermont (Wall Street Journal), 1960-1963 (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Ruggles, Richard, 1951-1962 (Box-folder 32: 16)
  - Salant, Walter S., 1958-1972 (Box-folder 32: 17)
  - Salera, Virgil, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 32: 18)
  - Samuels, Len H., 1959-1961 (Box-folder 32: 19)
  - Samuelson, Paul A., 1951-1966 (Box-folder 32: 20)
  - San Diego Chamber of Commerce (Max Schetter), 1977 (Box-folder 32: 21)
  - Saulnier, Raymond J., 1950-1960 (Box-folder 32: 22)
  - Savage, Leonard J., 1952-1955 (Box-folder 32: 23)
  - Sawyer, John A., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32: 24)
  - Schmidt, Emerson P., 1950-1964 (Box-folder 32: 25)
  - Schultz, Theodore W., 1948-1965 (Box-folder 32: 26)
  - Selden, Richard, 1951-1961 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Seldon, Arthur, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Seltzer, Lawrence H., 1947-1958 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Shapiro, Eli, 1955-1962 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Shaw, Edward S., 1947-1964 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Shaw, R. Harland, 1962 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Shea, George (Wall Street Journal), 1963 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Sheinbaum, Stanley K., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Shenfield, Arthur A., 1968-1972 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Shenoy, B. R., 1958-1965 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Shere, Louis, 1948-1959 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Shiskin, Julius, 1955-1968 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Shoup, Carl S., 1946-1959 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Shugg, Roger W. (Alfred A. Knopf, Inc.), 1948-1966 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Shultz, George P., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 33: 15)